pcspeedcat.com 2016-03-20

# PC SpeedCAT - The Pinnacle of PC Speed Evolution

## The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices.

We may share your unique identifying information with outside parties when they are helping us fulfill your order. We have safeguards in place (strong encryption, passwords, and limited access policies) to protect your information on our systems and when being communicated to our order fulfillment partners, such as the payment processor. 

In order for the complete order process to take place, SpeedCAT, LLC may share your information with our secure partners. This information is used for the designation of accounts and for a more seamless customer experience. SpeedCAT, LLC or its partners may use your contact information for internal or third party marketing purposes to offer you more SpeedCAT, LLC products or services, third party technical support, and related services, but your information will never be sold to an outside vendor. Information sharing may include but is not limited to: when your click or call is forwarded to a partner company who is an expert at providing Technical Support in your country or when your click or call is forwarded to a partner company who is an expert at providing Order Processing in your country. This information is transferred using secure lines and servers and may include but is not limited to: your name, email address, telephone number, purchase history with SpeedCAT, LLC, or IP address. Likewise, these third party vendors may share similar information with SpeedCAT, LLC for customer experience or marketing purposes. 

If you purchase any SpeedCAT, LLC software from a third party vendor information such as (but not limited to) your name, email address, IP address, and purchase information will be sent back from the vendor to SpeedCAT, LLC for order tracking purposes. If you purchase any SpeedCAT, LLC software and later decide to purchase any Technical Support as a result of an offer that was made to you after speaking with a representative of our partner your purchase information and your contact information will also be sent back to SpeedCAT, LLC from these third party partners for order tracking and customer care purposes. 

We use a cookie so you don't see our pop-up offer more than once per day. The cookie contains the date you saw our popup. If you have disabled cookies in your web browser, you'll see our popup offer every time you exit our web site. SpeedCAT, LLC applications may send anonymous usage data to SpeedCAT, LLC LLC. We use this information to track visitors' movement in the aggregate, and to gather general information about which screens are being accessed to improve the overall customer experience. 

SpeedCAT, LLC's Revenue Partners program provide site traffic to www.pcspeedCAT.com in exchange for a percentage of sales revenue. When you order a SpeedCAT, LLC product and you have been referred by a Revenue Partner, the following anonymous information is provided to the Revenue Partner to calculate revenue and verify our compliance: order number, product name, product cost, and date/time. **No customer identifying information is provided to Revenue Partners unless that Revenue Partner is responsible for helping us fulfill your order, in which case your personal information will only be used by Revenue Partner to fulfill your order.** SpeedCAT, LLC is not responsible for information you choose to provide directly to a SpeedCAT, LLC Revenue Partner via their web site. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products and services. Miscellaneous optional information collected on the order form, such as connection speed and operating system, are used in aggregate to help us make decisions about developing new products and services. Contact information you provide on your order form may be used occasionally by SpeedCAT, LLC or select partners to announce free updates to software items ordered, special offers and related promotions. You may opt out of this at any time. We are committed to respecting your wishes for use of your personal data. 

Software for mobile devices may include additional software and/or functionality to report to SpeedCAT, LLC and/or one or more third parties certain analytical data regarding your use of the applicable software (collectively, “Analytical Data”). All third party providers that analyze, collect, receive or process Analytical Data from us or on our behalf are prohibited from using such Analytical Data except on our behalf. All Analytical Data that is collected by SpeedCAT, LLC will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. SpeedCAT, LLC uses passwords and SSL encryption to protect the security of this information. 

### Other SpeedCAT, LLC Software 

Our software may include links or recommendations for other SpeedCAT, LLC products that would complement your current purchase. If you decide to activate an account and provide us with your email address, you will be automatically subscribed to receive SpeedCAT, LLC’s periodic newsletter (SpeedElite) in the form of an html email, with information including, but not limited to, software updates, discount offers, and new software releases. If you do not wish to receive these announcements, you can remove your name from our mailing list by the unsubscribe process detailed at the bottom of each newsletter or contact SpeedCAT, LLC via our website at www.pcspeedCATCenter.com and request to be removed from our list. SpeedCAT, LLC does not sell or trade customer information. Any customer contact information is kept private and never given out or sold to a third party. 

### Correct/Update 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * You can send us email at the SpeedCAT, LLC Support Center. 
  * You can send mail to the following postal address: 

SpeedCAT, LLC LLC,   
500 Westover Drive, Suite 9589   
Sanford, NC 27330   
You can call the following telephone number: 1.215.320.6000 

### Legal Disclaimer 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

### Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: 

SpeedCAT, LLC Webmaster,   
500 Westover Drive, Suite 9589   
Sanford, NC 27330
